almamaterstore.in 2014-12-01

# Privacy Policy

There are some basic terms and conditions that you need to be aware of while making a purchase on almamaterstore.in

#### Privacy Policy:

Thank you for visiting our web site. This privacy policy tells you how we use personal information collected at this site. Please read this privacy policy before using the site or submitting any personal information. By using the site, you are accepting the practices described in this privacy policy. These practices may be changed, but any changes will be posted and changes will only apply to activities and information on a going forward, not retroactive basis. You are encouraged to review the privacy policy whenever you visit the site to make sure that you understand how any personal information you provide will be used.

**Collection of Information** : We collect personally identifiable information, like names, postal addresses, email addresses, etc., when voluntarily submitted by our visitors. The information you provide is used to fulfill you specific request. This information is only used to fulfill your specific request, unless you give us permission to use it in another manner, for example to add you to one of our mailing lists.

**Cookie/Tracking Technology** : The Site may use cookie and tracking technology depending on the features offered. Cookie and tracking technology are useful for gathering information such as browser type and operating system, tracking the number of visitors to the Site, and understanding how visitors use the Site. Cookies can also help customize the Site for visitors. Personal information cannot be collected via cookies and other tracking technology, however, if you previously provided personally identifiable information, cookies may be tied to such information. Aggregate cookie and tracking information may be shared with third parties.

**Distribution of Information :** We may share information with governmental agencies or other companies assisting us in fraud prevention or investigation. We may do so when: (1) permitted or required by law; or, (2) trying to protect against or prevent actual or potential fraud or unauthorized transactions; or, (3) investigating fraud which has already taken place. The information is not provided to these companies for marketing purposes.

**Commitment to Data Security** : Your personally identifiable information is kept secure. Only authorized employees, agents and contractors (who have agreed to keep information secure and confidential) have access to this information. All emails and newsletters from this site allow you to opt out of further mailings.

**Privacy Contact Information :** If you have any questions, concerns, or comments about our privacy policy you may contact us using the information below: By e-mail: info@almamaterstore.in By Phone: 08041466559

#### User Account, Password, and Security:

You will receive a password and account designation upon completing the Website's registration process. You are responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of the password and account, and are fully responsible for all activities that occur under your password or account. You agree to (a) immediately notify Alma Mater of any unauthorized use of your password or account or any other breach of security, and (b) ensure that you exit from your account at the end of each session. Alma Mater cannot and will not be liable for any loss or damage arising from your failure to comply with this.

#### Limited User:

You agree and undertake not to reverse engineer, modify, copy, distribute, transmit, display, perform, reproduce, publish, license, create derivative works from, transfer, or sell any information or software obtained from almamaterstore.in. Limited reproduction and copying of the content of the website is permitted provided that Alma Mater's name is stated as the source and prior written permission of Alma Mater is sought. For the removal of doubt, it is clarified that unlimited or wholesale reproduction, copying of the content for commercial or non-commercial purposes and unwarranted modification of data and information within the content of the website is not permitted.

#### Delivery Policy

We usually take 7-8 working days for delivery from the date you place the order. Please note this delivery timeline is for the Insitution Store and Alma Mater Store Products only. For Bulk Orders ordered using the Play Tool the delivery timelines range from 12-15 days. We use our logistic partners for deliveries. Our logistic partners are Aramex and Blue Dart. If you want more details about delivery you can mail us with your order with the information shared with via email when you placed your order. 

If you want more details about tracking your order, you can mail us with your order no. at info@almamaterstore.in or call to our customer care from 09.30 AM to 06.30 PM at 08041466559.

#### Cancellation Policy

If you are not satisfied or if you find any fault with our product, just inform us along with the Order no. within 3 days of receiving the goods. Also return back the goods in the original condition for us to replace the order. However for any Bulk Orders ordered using the Play Tool the cancellation and returns are subject to management approval. For this you will have to get in touch with us via email or phone.

If you want more details about replacement, you can mail us with your order no. at info@almamaterstore.in or call to our customer care from 09.30 AM to 06.30 PM at 08041466559.

#### Refund Policy

If you are not satisfied with our product just inform the details along with the order no. and return back the goods within 3 days in original condition, so that we can refund your money back (Except shipping charges). However for any Bulk Orders ordered using the Play Tool the cancellation and returns are subject to management approval. For this you will have to get in touch with us via email or phone.

For any queries regarding the Terms and Conditions get in touch with us:

Alma Mater Store Pvt LtdNo 209, 18th main, 4th cross, 6th BlockKoramangala,Bangalore - 560095Phone : 08041466559Email : info@almamaterstore.in
